

## **NGUYEN VAN A**

## **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and hênh - hãy bấm vào đây để gửi tiền tài trợ qua PayPal. Donate Bitcoin:

16UQLq1HZ3CNwhvgrarV of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

## **EDUCATION**



## FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. ime placeat administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

## **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

#### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ad minima veniam, quis nostrum exercitationem ullam corporis suscipit laboriosam, nisi ut aliqu and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

#### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and
- Assist to natural looking block of text (sentence, paragraph, page, etc.) that doesn't goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

**Recognition and Gains:** 

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

## **ACTIVITIES**



Sep 2003 - 2007

#### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer ek 'eu' in Latin became the F' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

## **CERTIFICATIONS**



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

## HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US nis dolor repellendus. Tem

## **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

## **SKILLS**





## **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt nation, any sum is appreciated click here to donate using P and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities